# PEDRO HENRIQUE STAUB

### **Contact**

- +55 51 99717-7824
- https://portfolio-five-iota-85.vercel.app
- ppedrohstaub@gmail.com

### **Education**

#### **UNISC**

COMPUTER SCIENCES 2017 - 2019 Incompleted

#### **SENAC**

IT TECHNICIAN
2015 - 2016 Completed

### Skills

- PHP
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Mysql
- Docker
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Github
- VueJs
- Linux
- SQL
- Integration
- Implementation

### **About Me**

I have worked with web development since 2019, providing softwares to private security companies. The solutions I builded with my team have a daily impact on over 100.000 users around the world.

I am searching for new opportunities where I can apply my knowledge and experience built over the years and overcome new challenges.

## **Experience**

#### Junior Developer

Solutio Software

2019 - Currently

Solutio Software is a software house focused on the private security market, and it's main goal is to facilitate internal processes through automation and operational costs reduction.

- I have coded the website and many web softwares.
- Technologies: PHP, Javascript (JQuery), Mysql, Docker, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Github, VueJs, Linux Desktop e Server.
- I led a 3 person team.
- I developed integrations between softwares using API's and scripts for integration between databases.
- Participated in implementations remotely and presentially at customers.

#### **IT Assistant**

Cindapa

2017 - 2019

Cindapa is a private security company that provides security and surveillance services for customers in Brazil.

- Network, servers and computer support and maintenance.
- CCTV Installation and configuration.